♪I'll go with you to see your favorite flower in spring♪
♪سأذهب معك لرؤية زهرتك ​​المفضلة في الربيع♪
♪I'll treat you to your favorite ice cream in summer♪
♪ سأقدم لك الآيس كريم المفضل لديك في الصيف ♪
♪I'll be with you in the rain when you're sad in autumn♪
♪ سأكون معك تحت المطر عندما تكون حزيناً في الخريف ♪
♪I'll build a snowman for you in winter♪
♪ سأبني لك رجل ثلج في الشتاء ♪
♪Only you can have my romance♪
♪ أنت فقط من تستطيع الحصول على رومانسيتي ♪
♪Everyone else is secondary♪
♪ الجميع ثانوي ♪
♪I like your every smile and frown♪
♪ أحب كل ابتسامتك وعبوسك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪I want to take you to watch the stars♪
♪أريد أن آخذك لمشاهدة النجوم♪
♪Please♪
♪من فضلك♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪ دعني أعتني بك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪When it's cold, hide in my arms♪
♪ عندما يكون الجو بارداً، إختبئ بين ذراعي ♪
♪Drive all your sadness♪
♪ تخلص من كل حزنك ♪
♪Completely away♪
♪بعيد تمامًا♪
=Falling In Love With Me= =Episode 13=
=الوقوع في حبي= =الحلقة 13=
Mom.
أم.
The three days are up.
انتهت الأيام الثلاثة.
What?
ماذا؟
Go home.
اذهب للمنزل.
No, Mom.
لا امي.
Let's go home.
لنذهب إلى المنزل.
I haven't practiced singing yet.
- لم أتدرب على الغناء بعد.
Practicing what, Erbao?
أتدرب على ماذا يا إرباو؟
Face the reality.
مواجهة الواقع.
No.
لا.
I can't give up.
لا أستطيع الاستسلام.
Mom, Dad,
أمي أبي،
please give me one more chance.
من فضلك اعطينى فرصة اضافية.
I really love music.
أنا حقا أحب الموسيقى.
A deal's a deal.
الصفقة هي الصفقة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
Wait.
انتظر.
She can't go.
لا يمكنها الذهاب.
Why?
لماذا؟
Tong Yuxin,
تونغ يوكسين,
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
Tang,
تانغ،
do you mean...?
هل تعني...؟
Mr. Tong
السيد تونغ
and Mrs. Tong,
والسيدة تونغ،
I'll back Tong Yuxin up.
سأدعم تونغ يوكسين.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
whether she wants to sing
سواء كانت تريد الغناء
or not is up to her.
أم لا الأمر متروك لها.
She can do whatever she wants,
يمكنها أن تفعل ما تريد،
as long as you
طالما انك
agree to let her stay with me.
أوافق على السماح لها بالبقاء معي.
Tong Yuxin,
تونغ يوكسين,
do you accept me?
هل تقبلين بي؟
Look how happy she is.
أنظر كم هي سعيدة.
I...
أنا...
Tong Yuxin, Tong Erbao,
تونغ يوكسين، تونغ إرباو،
I like you!
أنا معجب بك!
Be my girl...
كوني فتاتي...
There are so many people.
هناك الكثير من الناس.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Stay calm.
ابق هادئا.
We'll see.
سوف نرى.
Who are these two?
من هما هذان؟
They are my parents.
هم والداي.
Dad, Mom,
أبي أمي،
my name is Liang Tete.
اسمي ليانغ تيتي.
Please sit.
اجلس لطفا.
You look quite young.
تبدو شابًا جدًا.
I'm a junior in college.
أنا مبتدئ في الكلية.
A college student?
طالب جامعي؟
You're the same age as Erbao.
أنت في نفس عمر إرباو.
It's pretty good.
انها جيدة جدا.
Our girl didn't even get into college.
فتاتنا لم تدخل الكلية حتى
What's the big deal?
ما هي الصفقة الكبيرة؟
I think Erbao
أعتقد إرباو
is better than many college students.
أفضل من العديد من طلاب الجامعات.
No, cousin, why are you here?
لا يا ابن العم لماذا أنت هنا؟
Cousin?
ابن عم؟
Mr. and Mrs. Tong,
السيد والسيدة تونغ،
my cousin doesn't know any better.
ابن عمي لا يعرف أي شيء أفضل.
I'll take him away.
سوف آخذه بعيدا.
I'm not a kid.
أنا لست طفلا.
What do I not know?
ماذا لا أعرف؟
What I mean is
ما أعنيه هو
my feelings for Tong Yuxin are serious.
مشاعري تجاه تونغ يوكسين جادة.
Then tell us
ثم أخبرنا
what you like about Erbao.
ما يعجبك في ارباو.
She is very kind,
هي لطيفة جدا،
very serious
جدي جدا
and very talented.
وموهوب جدا.
She writes great songs.
إنها تكتب أغاني رائعة.
She's very attractive when she plays the guitar.
إنها جذابة للغاية عندما تعزف على الجيتار.
That's me?
هذا أنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
I see.
أرى.
It's all inherited from you, Mrs. Tong.
كل هذا ورث منك يا سيدة تونغ.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Aren't you a sweet talker.
لا أنت المتكلم الحلو.
Tang,
تانغ،
what about you?
ماذا عنك؟
What do you think is good about Erbao?
ما الذي تعتقد أنه جيد في إرباو؟
In my eyes, she is good
في نظري هي طيبة
in every way.
بكل الطرق.
Yutong, are you bewitched?
يوتونغ، هل أنت مسحور؟
Okay.
تمام.
You guys can go back.
يا رفاق يمكن أن تعود.
Let us have some peace.
دعونا نحظى ببعض السلام.
Mom, we're not leaving then.
أمي، نحن لن نغادر بعد ذلك.
You now have a personal thing to deal with.
لديك الآن شيء شخصي للتعامل معه.
Shouldn't we stick around and see?
ألا يجب أن نبقى ونرى؟
Honey,
عسل،
let's go upstairs.
لنصعد السلالم.
Come on, Erbao.
هيا يا ارباو.
Liang Tete,
ليانج تيتي,
what kind of tricks are you playing?
ما نوع الحيل التي تلعبها؟
Yutong,
يوتونغ،
I want to pursue Tong Yuxin.
أريد متابعة Tong Yuxin.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
She's my first love whom I've been looking for all along.
إنها حبي الأول الذي كنت أبحث عنه طوال الوقت.
She's the reason why I want to be a singer.
إنها السبب وراء رغبتي في أن أصبح مغنية.
Yutong,
يوتونغ،
I want to be with her.
اريد ان اكون معها.
You'll help me, won't you?
سوف تساعدني، أليس كذلك؟
Fine.
بخير.
You're free to marry whoever you love
أنت حر في الزواج بمن تحب
since you married and divorced
منذ أن تزوجت وطلقت
without considering my feelings.
دون مراعاة لمشاعري.
I won't show up at your wedding.
لن أحضر في حفل زفافك.
Just consider me as a dead son.
فقط اعتبرني كابن ميت.
♪Until the equator's light melts Antarctica♪
♪حتى يذوب ضوء خط الاستواء القارة القطبية الجنوبية♪
♪Your love for me♪
♪حبك لي♪
What is it? It's so catchy.
ما هذا؟  انها جذابة جدا.
I wrote it.
لقد كتبت ذلك.
It's called "Equator and Antarctica".
يطلق عليه "خط الاستواء والقارة القطبية الجنوبية".
You wrote it?
انت كتبتها؟
So talented!
موهوب جدا!
Are you a singer?
هل أنت مغني؟
Not right now.
ليس الآن.
But I love music.
لكني أحب الموسيقى.
Music helps me forget my troubles
الموسيقى تساعدني على نسيان مشاكلي
and allows me to hear my inner voice.
ويسمح لي بسماع صوتي الداخلي.
That's right.
صحيح.
Send all the trouble away!
إرسال كل المشاكل بعيدا!
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Which college are you in?
في أي كلية أنت؟
I'm Tong Erbao.
أنا تونغ إرباو.
I'm not from around here.
أنا لست من هنا.
I'm here for a singer-songwriter contest.
أنا هنا من أجل مسابقة المغني وكاتب الأغاني.
A contest?
مسابقة؟
I bet you'll snag an award.
أراهن أنك سوف تحصل على جائزة.
Can I come watch you play again tomorrow?
هل يمكنني الحضور لمشاهدتك تلعب مرة أخرى غدًا؟
Yes!
نعم!
♪Until the equator's light embraces the Antarctica♪
♪ حتى يحتضن ضوء خط الاستواء القارة القطبية الجنوبية ♪
♪Maybe I can embrace you too♪
♪ ربما أستطيع احتضانك أيضًا ♪
♪Even though that's the farthest Antarctica♪
♪ على الرغم من أن هذه هي أبعد القارة القطبية الجنوبية ♪
(I Am a Singer-songwriter Audition) Missy, are you kidding?
(أنا تجربة أداء للمغني وكاتب الأغاني) هل تمزحين يا ميسي؟
(Tong Erbao, come on) You write good songs,
(تونغ إرباو، هيا) أنت تكتب أغاني جيدة،
but a singer needs to sing well.
لكن المغني يحتاج إلى الغناء بشكل جيد.
Give me one more chance, please.
أعطني فرصة أخرى، من فضلك.
I will strive hard.
سأسعى جاهدا.
Missy, go back to school.
ميسي، عودي إلى المدرسة.
You have no talent as a singer.
ليس لديك موهبة كمغنية.
Such poor singing skills.
هذه مهارات الغناء السيئة.
What makes she think she can be a singer?
ما الذي يجعلها تعتقد أنها يمكن أن تكون مغنية؟
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
You know nothing about music.
أنت لا تعرف شيئا عن الموسيقى.
Tong Erbao!
تونغ ارباو!
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪In the few weeks after breaking up♪
♪ في الأسابيع القليلة بعد الانفصال ♪
♪I restrain myself from missing you♪
♪ أنا أمنع نفسي من أن أفتقدك ♪
♪Like a chronic disease, it comes and goes♪
♪ مثل المرض المزمن، يأتي ويذهب ♪
♪Maybe I'm to blame for loving too deeply♪
♪ ربما أنا الملام على الحب العميق ♪
♪Will time heal the heartbreak♪
♪ هل الزمن سيشفي حسرة القلب ♪
♪Or will it make it more painful♪
♪ أم أنه سيجعل الأمر أكثر إيلاما ♪
♪Missing you is an incurable disease♪
♪ اشتياقك داء لا شفاء منه ♪
♪Yet now I think of you again♪
♪ والآن أفكر فيك مرة أخرى ♪
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪I am not afraid of lonely nights♪
♪أنا لا أخاف من الليالي المنعزلة♪
♪Everyone knows it is a lie♪
♪ الجميع يعلم أنها كذبة ♪
♪I don't want to bear the pain of missing again♪
♪ لا أريد أن أتحمل ألم الافتقاد مرة أخرى ♪
♪Can you please let me go♪
♪هل يمكنك أن تسمح لي بالذهاب ♪
♪The carriage of time won't stop♪
♪ لن تتوقف عربة الزمن ♪
♪I'm sorry. I can't be the person you're with for the rest of your life♪
♪ أنا آسف.  لا أستطيع أن أكون الشخص الذي أنت معه لبقية حياتك ♪